This is Hong-Di-N China, one of the world's largest filming locations.
Historical sites such as the first Chinese Emperor's Palace and the Forbidden City
have been reproduced at an authentic size.
More than half of all the country's historical dramas are produced in this town.
Young people from all over China move here with dreams of achieving startup.
Because when I was young, I saw a lot of people in the movie.
So I wanted to see them.
Hey, the people are pretending.
Who are they pretending?
I'm still in my heart.
I have a lot of confidence.
I'll be out soon.
However, most of the jobs they actually get are as extras,
also called background actors.
And the pay is extremely low.
In this tough industry, where connections are crucial
and fraud is common.
Aspiring actors continue to pursue their dreams,
they're known as Hundian Drifters.
behind the glamour of the silver screen.
This episode depicts the untold drama
of the Hundian drifters.
Early in the morning, people seeking jobs
as background actors gather on a street corner.
I don't know.
I know.
Zhongjiand, came to Hongjiang ten years ago, when he was 36.
Hopeful extras first need to register with the actors' union.
Anyone can get certification as an extra if they shall ID and pay a $1 commission.
In recent years the Chinese film industry has picked up momentum along with the nation's
economic growth leading to major demand for bid parts.
A total of 80,000 people have come to Hong-Di-N chasing the Chinese dream.
Some have made it big but success stories are extremely rare.
I have a hundred percent of it.
How much?
I have a birthday party.
I don't have a birthday party.
Early one morning, shooting began on set for a drama about the Chinese Communist Party fighting in the revolution,
before the founding of modern China.
Menario is a popular one.
Zhang was hired to play a soldier in the background.
Originally from a rural farming village,
Zhang had worked in factories outside of his hometown,
but he tired of the monotonous work and came to Heng Di'en
when a friend invited him.
He believes he's got what it takes to become a true actor.
But recently, he's been getting acting tips from less experienced extras.
There are two ranks for extras.
One's without spoken lines are called the masses and make about ten US dollars a day.
with their own lines are called special background actors
and make several hundred dollars in some cases.
But only a handful of extras obtain this coveted position.
Zung has been an extra for ten years,
but has yet to escape the so-called masses.
Shooting often drags on for long hours.
But Zung says he's never considered changing jobs.
I don't like to say that.
When you open the company,
I don't know how to say it.
I'm the biggest dancer in the world.
I'm not a dancer.
You're so good.
I'm so good.
I'm so good at it.
But I don't want to say it.
I can say it.
I see the little girl.
The little girl.
I can't say it.
The work of extras can hardly be called safe.
Shooting continued until early the next day.
Pay for the day was $12.
Extras get a pay slip with their names and wages written on them
and exchange them for cash elsewhere.
Zung Rinse Room outside Hungdian for $80 a month.
His fellow drifters came by for a visit.
Then I said to myself,
You know, there is no way out.
I am not a big fan.
But I'm a little bit.
I think I am a little too much.
I still think that I should do this.
I think I should do this.
I think he should do this.
He should do this.
I should do this.
That's what I think.
I don't think that I should do this.
He should do this.
Jiang Lan, heels from Chongqing, located 1,300 kilometers west of Hongdean.
She worked at a company back home, but came here three years ago hoping to become
an actress. Today, extras gathered at five in the morning for a shoot. Most of them are in their
twenties and thirties. The film is about the threat of invasion before the PRC's founding.
Extras play the role of student demonstrators.
Dramas focusing on patriotism are common subject in China.
Jiong shares a 20 square meter room with a friend.
Rent is $80 a month.
I met my first wife in the city of Changjian in the first month of the year.
I met her at home and she left.
I met her again in the second month.
I went to the capital and I met her two or three friends.
She was so tired and I was so tired.
After I came back, I found that my family was in the big door.
So I went to the bank and slept at night.
I went to the hospital with a cold.
When I was in the airport, I cried.
I was so angry.
I went to the airport to see the big street.
I said,
I was going to the airport after I got to work.
your image,
your age,
you want to come out.
It's too hard.
And then,
you need to change a lot of places.
You still need a person to take you.
You still need to write a letter.
This is the way to write a old sentence.
If this kind of thing is possible to have a real child,
the last child will be in his hands.
Then what should I do?
So I don't have this plan,
I just think I have a problem now.
So the last one is the past.
But I want to go to the work,
and change the better life environment.
Then I'll communicate with you,
you'll have to lie tomorrow.
Many under-employed extras also work as street vendors.
The majority of them have trouble getting by on their acting income alone.
have trouble getting by on their acting income alone.
We call themUsuals
They don't use your equipment
They have a group of our staff
A group of our friends
Who could get to the right place?
I heard the cat
I heard the sound from the cat
Didn't they report on the news?
They did
They did not report on my news
The people of San Marra people
I have two people
They report on it
They are all related
It's all related
It's a little short
They are all related
There is one more
Ten-minute
Although the Chinese film industry grew rapidly, it's recently been showing signs of a decline.
Due to a slowdown in economic growth, stricter censorship and crackdowns on tax evasion,
Investments into films have dropped.
Fewer movies are making it to the big screen.
The first ones to be hit by the downturn
are the Hengdean Drifters.
I have been running for a few days.
Yes.
Now, if you don't want to say that,
don't think it's too far.
I feel like I'm in a lot of trouble.
Zung experiences more days without work.
Even so, he says his only dream is to stay in Hengdian.
He's not young enough to be hired on the spotted factories.
And he doesn't want to return home to be a farmer.
To gain sight income, he and his friends decided
to collect and sell empty cans and plastic models.
The next location is a hillside on the outskirts of Hundien.
and usually large number of extras are called together.
They're here for a drama depicting the Communist Party Army's advances.
Zung is among the extras playing soldiers.
During the break, many extras take out their smartphones and start talking on that.
They're filming clips to upload on QUI, a smartphone app for sharing short videos.
QUI is hugely popular in China now, with more than 700 million users.
The number of likes gained from followers can be exchanged for money.
It's a new opportunity for struggling drifters to earn just a little more income.
The view is so clear.
The view is so long.
You have to record a classic video.
And the view is so clear.
You have to have a good view.
The view is so clear.
We have to take a picture.
This is the way.
Let's go.
Ji-Yong has also started a new project.
She plans to produce her own drama series and distributed online.
She thinks up the plot herself.
To reduce costs, she prepares all the costumes and props herself as well.
The drama is about life in a Chinese dynasty castle.
As they use movie sets from where they work, they can avoid location costs.
Jiangs fellow extras work together and plan to share profits if the project is successful.
Jiangs housemate Dandong also performs in the drama.
They edit scenes on their smartphones, slowly but surely they plan to create 30 episodes.
Ji-ong distributed some of the episodes online
and is gaining more followers.
I think it's a good mentality.
Because you don't want to be too hopeful.
You want to be 80%
But if you don't succeed, you won't be too greedy.
If you want to be 100% greedy, you can be greedy.
You think you're greedy.
I don't want to be too greedy.
So you think I'm going to find a guy here.
What's the situation now?
What's your relationship with someone?
How do you discuss your problems?
What's the most important thing to be a new person?
Yes, the most important thing to be a new person.
For example, we still have a lot of things to discuss.
But what do you think about the end of the year?
After the end of the year,
we went to the end of the year.
But it's still a single day.
So I have to go.
I have to go. I have to go.
I'm going to the city with some friends.
Jobs have been scarce, but he finally got a chance to gain some much needed income.
Zung and the other extras have been hired to help live and up an event for a health food pyramid scheme
I'm not going to go.
Multilevel marketing has created issues in China,
ballooning into a serious social problem.
After finishing work,
the Hong-Dien Drifters continue to pursue their dreams,
amidst the rough job market.
Put it down.
There's a phrase here that some people say with genuine positivity, while others speak
it with irony.
The only talent you need to succeed in Hong-Dien is the ability to keep on dreaming.
Like Maul's Lord to a Street lap, there are always more dreamers swarming to Hong-Dien.